A Guide to the Papers of the Virginia Quarterly Review, 1925-1935
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Chambrun, Jacques 1928-1930, 87 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 9)
- Chambrun, Jacques 1931-1935, 154 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 9)
- Chandler, J.A.C. 1925, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Chase, E.P. 1930-1932, 16 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Chase, Lewis 1929, 10 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Chase, Stuart 1929-1935, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Cheney, Sheldon 1935, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Cher, Marie 1932, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Child, Richard Washburn 1925 January 14, 1 l. ALS, to Virginia Quarterly Review. (Box 10)
- Childs, James Rives 1928-1930, 2 items. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Childs (Box 10)
- Chinard, Gilbert 1928-1932, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Christie, Margaret 1929-1932, 15 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Christy, Arthur 1933, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Chubb, Thomas Caldecot 1934-1935, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Church, Richard 1929-1931, 15 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Church, S.R. 1927-1928, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Clark, Barrett H. 1926-1932, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Clark, Harry H. 1925-1932, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Clark, William Andrews, Jr. 1925, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Clarke, George Herbert 1925-1934, 52 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Clay, Henry 1933-1934, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Cleaton, Allen 1928-1933, 23 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Clemens, J.R. 1930-1933, 18 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Clemons, Harry 1927-1935, 14 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Clements, Albert E. 1928-1933, 17 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Cleveland, Philip Jerome 1933, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Clift, Ruth Sullivan 1931-1933, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Cloud, Virginia Woodward 1928-1931, 19 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Cobb, Irvin S. 1925 January 10, 1 l. TLS, Secretary of Cobb, to Virginia Quarterly Review. (Box 10)
- Coblentz, Stanton Arthur 1927-1934, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Cochran, Louis 1931-1932, 15 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Cockburn, Claud 1931-1933, 19 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Cocke, M. Estes 1930, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Coffin, Robert Peter Tristam 1926-1935, 115 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Cohn, David L. 1931-1935, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Coker, Francis W. 1935, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Cole, Carter S. 1927-1930, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Coleman, W.H. 1931, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Collins, Joseph 1925-1931, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Collins, Paul V. 1930, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 10)
- Colum, Padraic 1934-1935, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 11)
- Columbia University Press 1931-1933, 12 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 11)
- Colwell, Lewis 1931, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 11)
- Comfort, William Wistar 1927, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 11)
- Compton, Arthur H. 1929, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 11)
- Conklin, Edwin Grant 1927, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 11)
- Conner, R.D.W. 1929, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 11)
- Cook, Allen Blow 1929-1931, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 11)
- Coolidge, Archibald Cary 1926 April 2, 1 l. TLS to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 11)
- Corbin, John 1925 February 11, 1 l. ALS, to Virginia Quarterly Review. (Box 11)
- Cordell, Richard A. 1928 October 20, 1 l. TLS, to Virginia Quarterly Review. (Box 11)
- Corson, John J. 1934-1935, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 11)
- Cortissoz, Royal 1925 January 10, 1 l. TLS, to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 11)
- Couch, W.T. 1925-1935, 70 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 11)
- Cournos, John 1928-1936, 76 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 11)
- Coward-McCann, Inc. 1929-1934, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 11)
- Cox, Eleanor Rogers 1925, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 11)
- Cox, James M. 1928 October 16, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Cox (Box 11)
- Cox, Marvin 1934, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 11)
- Coyle, David Cushman 1934-1935, 40 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 11)
- Crabites, Pierre 1926-1929, 48 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 11)
- Crabites, Pierre 1930-1933, 46 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 11)
- Craig, Hardin 1925, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 11)
- Crane, Hart 1927, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 11)
- Crane, Richard 1931, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 11)
- Craven, Avery 1932-1934, 18 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 11)
- Crawford, Bruce 1925-1935, 53 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 11)
- Crawford, Horace D 1930-1931, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 11)
- Crawford, Phyllis 1930, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 11)
- Creekmore, Hubert 1934-1935, 6 items. Letters, Virginia Quarterly Review to Creekmore (Box 12)
- Crenshaw, Lewis D. 1925, 3 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 12)
- Crenshaw, Mary Mayo 1925-1926, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 12)
- Cross, Wilbur Lucius 1932, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 12)
- Crothers, Rachel n.d., 2 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 12)
- Crouse, Russel 1932, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 12)
- Thomas Y. Crowell Company 1927-1930, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 12)
- Cumming, Hugh S. 1925-1930, 4 items. (Box 12)
- Cumming, Lucy (Mrs. Hugh) n.d., 3 pp. ALS, to Virginia Quarterly Review. (Box 12)
- Cunningham, Harry F. 1931-1934, 14 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 12)
- Curle, Richard 1934 June 12, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Curle (Box 12)
- Curry, Kathryn Worth 1931-1934, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 12)
- Cuthbert, Clifton 1928-1932, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 12)
- Miscellaneous C 1925-1935, ca. 500 items. Miscellaneous authors, correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review. (Box 12)
- Dabbs, James McBride 1929-1935, 16 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 13)
- Dabney, Richard Heath 1930 December 12, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Dabney (Box 13)
- Dabney, Thomas L. 1926-1927, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 13)
- Dabney, Virginius 1925-1935, 47 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 13)
- Damrau, Frederic 1926-1931, 32 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 13)
- Dandridge, E.P. 1930, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 13)
- Daniels, Josephus 1926-1929, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 13)
- Dannenbaum, Raymond 1935, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 13)
- Dargan, Edwin Preston 1925-1935, 44 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 13)
- Dargan, Olive 1927-1935, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 13)
- Darling, H. Maurice 1929, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 13)
- Davidson, Donald 1926-1935, 49 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 13)
- Davidson, Gustav 1928-1930, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 13)
- Davidson, Mabel 1925-1934, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 13)
- Davis, Arthur Kyle 1925-1933, 51 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 13)
- Davis, Elmer 1926-1932, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 13)
- Davis, Jackson 1930, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 13)
- Davis, Jerome Charles 1927-1931, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 13)
- Davis, John Allen 1929, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 13)
- Davis, Joseph S. 1927-1934, 21 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 13)
- Davis, Lambert 1926-1930, 16 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 13)
- Davis, Malcom W. 1928 December 18, 1 l. Letter to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 13)
- Davis, Mary Lee 1928-1933, 23 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 13)
- Davis, William Harper 1931, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 13)
- Davison, Edward 1932, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 13)
- Davidson, Wilfred 1927-1928, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 13)
- John Day Company 1933-1934, 14 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 13)
- Dayden, J.R. 1927 October 17, 1 l. Letter to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 13)
- De Casseres, Benjamin 1928-1932, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 13)
- Decatur, Stephen 1928, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 13)
- De Ford, Miriam 1927-1934, 17 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 14)
- De Hueck, Baroness C. 1929, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 14)
- De Huff, Elizabeth Willis 1931-1935, 14 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 14)
- De Jong, David Cornel 1928-1935, 37 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 14)
- De La Mare, Walter 1928-1935, 16 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 14)
- De Madariaga, Salvador 1929 December 31, 1 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to De Madariaga (Box 14)
- Dennett, Tyler 1929, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 14)
- Dennis, Forbes 1932, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 14)
- Dennis, Lawrence 1934, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 14)
- Derleth, August William 1932-1935, 3 items. Letters, Virginia Quarterly Review to Derleth (Box 14)
- Deutsch, Babette 1925-1935, 101 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 14)
- De Voto, Bernard 1933-1934, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 14)
- De Vries, Peter n.d., 1 l. Copy of letter, to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 14)
- Dewey, John 1925-1934, 2 items. Letters, to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 14)
- Dick, Sheldon 1932-1933, 23 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 14)
- Dickinson, Edwin D. 1928, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 14)
- Dickinson, Thomas H. 1927-1930, 28 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 14)
- Dieffenbach, Albert C. 1927 October 5, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Dieffenbach (Box 14)
- Dillard, James Hardy 1927-1935, 16 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 14)
- Dillingham, Pauline 1928-1934, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 14)
- Dobie, Charles Caldwell 1925 March 6, 1 l. TLS, to Virginia Quarterly Review. (Box 14)
- Dodd, Martha 1934, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 14)
- Dodd, William Edward 1925-1935, 94 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 14)
- Dodd, Mead, and Co. 1928-1935, 21 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 14)
- Dodds, John W. 1932-1933, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 14)
- Dold, William Elliott 1925-1929, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 14)
- Dole, Nathan Haskell 1930, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 14)
- George H. Doran and Co. 1925-1927, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 14)
- Doré, M.B. 1927-1930, 18 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 14)
- Doubleday Doran and Co. 1928-1935, 85 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 15)
- Doubleday, Page, and Co. 1926-1927, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 15)
- Doughty, Le Garde S. 1933-1935, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 15)
- Douglas, Paul H. 1934 September 20, 1 l. TLS, with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 15)
- Douglass, Lucille 1928, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 15)
- Douglas, Norman 1933 March 17, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Douglas (Box 15)
- Downey, Harris 1933-1935, 25 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 15)
- Drake, W.M. 1928-1931, 10 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 15)
- Draper, George 1930 October 22, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Draper (Box 15)
- Drennon, Herbert 1927-1931, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 15)
- Dresbach, Glenn Ward 1930 July 29, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Dresbach (Box 15)
- Drewry, Carleton 1930-1931, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 15)
- Drewry, John E. 1927-1935, 12 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 15)
- Drucker, Peter 1935, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 15)
- Du Bois, Arthur E. 1932-1935, 12 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 15)
- Duffus, R. L. 1933, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 15)
- Dupee, Frederick 1935, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 15)
- Dutton, E.P., and Co. 1925-1932, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 15)
- Dyer, Walter A. 1928-1935, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 15)
- Dykstra, Leslie Thompson 1929-1933, 14 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 15)
- Miscellaneous D 1925-1935, ca. 200 items. Miscellaneous authors, correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review. (Box 15)
- Eaton, Walter Prichard 1932-1934, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 16)
- Eaton, Clement 1934-1935, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 16)
- Eberhart, Richard 1935, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 16)
- Edgar, Pelham 1934 April 6, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Edgar (Box 16)
- Edgar Allan Poe Shrine 1925-1926, 3 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 16)
- Edmunds, Abe Craddock 1927, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 16)
- Edmunds, Murrell 1925-1935, 15 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 16)
- Edwards, John B. 1929-1935, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 16)
- Eggleston, Joseph Dupuy 1925 February 26, 1 l. TLS, to Virginia Quarterly Review. (Box 16)
- Eliot, Thomas Stearns 1928-1935, 15 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 16)
- Elliott, G.R. 1925-1929, 15 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 16)
- Elliott, Mary Mallett 1931-1933, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 16)
- Elliott, W.Y. 1926-1934, 20 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 16)
- Ellis, Havelock 1928-1934, 12 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 16)
- Ellis, Wilmot E. 1926-1931, 30 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 16)
- Elmo, Ann 1935, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 16)
- England, Robert 1927-1935, 25 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 16)
- Erskine, Albert, Jr. 1935, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 16)
- Erskine, John 1925-1930, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 16)
- Eshleman, Lloyd Wendell 1931-1934, 14 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 16)
- Ethridge, Mark 1929-1930, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 16)
- Evans, Ernestine 1926-1935, 111 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 16)
- Ewell, Alice Maude 1925-1934, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 16)
- Miscellaneous E 1925-1935, ca. 150 items. Miscellaneous authors. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 16)
- Fachenthal, Frank D., 2 pp. ALS (draft), James Southall Wilson to Fachentahl, a personal letter (Box 17)
- Fadiman, Clifton 1930-1934, 12 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Fagan, Benjamin 1935, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Fagin, N. Bryllion 1926-1934, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Fairchild, Henry Pratt 1925-1934, 71 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Falkenau, R. 1928, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Farrar and Rinehart 1929-1935, 17 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Farrell, James T. 1933 June 1, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Farrell (Box 17)
- Faulkner, Harrison 1931-1932, 3 items. TL(carbons), Virginia Quarterly Review to Faulkner (Box 17)
- Faulkner, William 1934 December 29, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Faulkner (Box 17)
- Faust, Henri 1926-1930, 17 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Fay, C.R. 1928-1929, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Fay, Sidney Bradshaw 1931-1934, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Feibleman, James 1931-1935, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Fenellosa, Mary (McNeill) 1928-1930, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Ferrero, France 1925-1930, 4 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Ficke, Arthur Davison 1925 January 18, 1 l. ALS, to Virginia Quarterly Review. (Box 17)
- Fields, Harold 1929-1934, 14 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Fingerman, Charles 1928-1929, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Finley, John Huston 1924-1929, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Firkins, O.W. 1925-1927, 4 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Fischer, Louis 1927-1935, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Fishbein, Morris 1927, 4 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Fisher, Irving 1925-1927, 4 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review, with pamphlet (Box 17)
- Fisher, Mahlon Leonard 1927 January 22, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Fitch, James M., Jr. 1934-1935, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Fitzell, Lincoln 1932-1935, 26 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Flannagan, Roy 1930, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Fleming, Berry 1935, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Fletcher, John Gould 1928-1934, 19 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Flexner, Abraham 1924 December 22, 1 l. TLS, to Virginia Quarterly Review. (Box 17)
- Flexner, Simon, Secretary of 1925 January 20, 1 l. TLS, to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Flint, F. Cudworth 1935, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Flynn, Clarence Edwin 1926-1934, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Flynn, John T. 1935, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Foerster, Norman 1925-1929, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Follett, Wilson 1928-1935, 33 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 17)
- Ford, Charles Henri 1929 July 26, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Ford (Box 17)
- Ford, Robert D. 1925 May 1, 1 l. TLS to Virginia Quarterly Review, w/pamphlet (Box 17)
- Foreman, Clark 1930-1934, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 18)
- Forum Press 1929-1930, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 18)
- Fosdick, Raymond Blaine 1924-1929, 35 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 18)
- Fraenkel, Michael 1928-1929, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 18)
- Francis, Robert 1927-1935, 28 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 18)
- Frank, Jerome 1934, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 18)
- Frank, Waldo 1927-1935, 35 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 18)
- Franklin, Fabian 1927-1929, 14 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 18)
- Fraser, Alexander David 1932-1935, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 18)
- Freeman, Douglas Southall 1925-1935, 25 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 18)
- Freeman, Joseph 1931-1932, 22 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 18)
- Freeman, Margaret Waller 1933-1934, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 18)
- French, John C. 1926-1928, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 18)
- Freud, Sigmund 1934 September 14, 1 l. TL (carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Freud (Box 18)
- Freund, Philip 1931, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 18)
- Friend, Julius W. 1935, 28 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 18)
- Frierson, William C. 1929 March 26, 1 l. TL (carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Frierson (Box 18)
- Frost, Frances 1928-1935, 72 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 18)
- Frost, Robert 1927-1929, 4 items. TL (carbons), Virginia Quarterly Review to Frost (Box 18)
- Furnas, J.C. 1931-1932, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 18)
- Miscellaneous F 1925-1935, ca. 150 items. Miscellaneous authors. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 18)
- Gale, Esson 1927-1928, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Galsworthy, John 1929 June 27, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Galsworthy (Box 19)
- Gardner, George W. 1929 May 17, 1 l. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Garland, Hamlin May 19, 1 l. ALS, to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Garrett, Garet April 1, 2 l. ALS, to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Gaultier, Jules de [1928 July 10], 1 item. APCS, to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Gaunt, Paul 1934, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)